saferpass.net 2017-02-15

# SaferPass - The best password manager

PRIVACY POLICY This privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") explains the privacy practices of SaferPass, a product of SaferPass s.r.o., a corporation (hereinafter "SaferPass", "we", "us" or "our") that apply to (i) the access and use of the www.SaferPass.net website, and any related sub-domains, which are operated by SaferPass (collectively the "Website"), (ii) download and use of our proprietary application (the "SaferPass Application") and (iii) the provision by SaferPass of services through the Website and the SaferPass Application (the "Services"). SaferPass IS COMMITTED TO MAINTAINING YOUR PRIVACY. PLEASE READ THROUGH ALL THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY SO THAT YOU UNDERSTAND WHAT TYPE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT, HOW WE COLLECT IT, HOW WE USE IT AND TO WHOM WE DISCLOSE IT. SaferPass GUIDING PRINCIPLES. The passwords you store in your SaferPass are encrypted on your device using a master password that only you know. Your passwords will be encrypted on your device and will be sent to SaferPass in encrypted form through a secure connection for storage in order to enable synchronization with your other devices. SaferPass never stores your master password on any server so your passwords can't be retrieved by anyone but you. When you need to access your passwords the decryption of your passwords is done on your device with your master password. Your passwords can only be accessed by you with your master password unless you decide to share or bequeath passwords with another SaferPass user. No SaferPass employee can ever access your passwords. PLEASE NOTE THAT THERE IS NO WAY TO RECOVER YOUR ACCOUNT IF YOU FORGET YOUR MASTER PASSWORD. We don't ask for your personal information unless we truly need it. We don’t store your personal information on SaferPass servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our Services. Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these principles: 1\. CONSENT. BY USING OUR WEBSITE OR THE SaferPass APPLICATION, OR BY SUBMITTING PERSONAL INFORMATION TO US, YOU CONSENT TO SaferPass'S COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF SUCH PERSONAL INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY (AS AMENDED FROM TIME TO TIME) AND AS PERMITTED OR REQUIRED BY LAW. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, do not provide us with any personal information or use any of the Services we offer on the Website or through the SaferPass Application. You can withdraw your consent at any time by following the instructions described below in the Section "QUESTIONS". 2\. AMENDMENTS AND NOTIFICATION OF PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES. We reserve the right to modify our Privacy Policy as necessary and will post a copy of the amended Privacy Policy on the Website. Please review it periodically to ensure that you are aware of any modifications. If we make any significant changes with regard to how we use your personal information, we will notify you in writing via the email address specified in your account or by posting a prominent notice on the Website. Any amendments to the Privacy Policy will be considered accepted by you if you continue to use the Website after any amendments have been posted on the Website. 3\. AN IMPORTANT NOTE FOR PARENTS AND LEGAL GUARDIANS. SaferPass respects the U.S. Children's Online Privacy Protection (COPPA) Act of 1998 and upholds the guidelines of the Children's Advertising Review Unit (CARU) of the Council of Better Business Bureau, Inc. in each of its websites for children. You can help by spending time online with your children and monitoring your children's online use. Please help us protect your child's privacy by instructing them never to provide personal information on this website or any other without your permission. If you are under the age of 18, please be sure to read this policy with your parents or legal guardians and ask questions about anything you do not understand. Children under the age of 13 (U13) are prohibited from using the Services provided by SaferPass. 4\. INFORMATION COLLECTION. SaferPass only collects personal information provided to us via the Website or the SaferPass Application during the completion of the registration form, during the use of our Services, during sign-up, payment for our Services or while providing feedback or comments. Collection is limited to the following information: name and email address (i) that we receive from our social networking partners (e.g., such as Facebook, Twitter or Google+) if you have chosen to subscribe to the Services through those partners; and/or (ii) that you have decided to make available to us and your contacts (e.g., pictures, email) either directly or through our social networking partners. This information also helps us communicate with you about your use of the Service, product announcements and software updates, as well as to respond to your requests for assistance. From time to time, we may want to contact you with information about product announcements, software updates and special offers. We also may want to contact you with information about products and services from our business partners. Opt-out: You may opt out of such communications at any time by contacting us support@saferpass.net directly. SaferPass may also collect the following usage information, whether you are using the Website or using the SaferPass Application as a registered or non-registered user: your IP address, SaferPass cookie information (see below for more information), the date and time of your visit or use of the SaferPass Application, the type of internet browser or hardware device (computer or mobile/smartphone) you are using, the URL of any other website that referred you to our Website or the SaferPass Application, URLs of the pages you visit, in order to provide you with a better user experience. This information is not associated or linked to you as an individual and is not generally regarded as personal information unless you register for our Services. In the event of your registration, that information does become personal information as it is linked with the personal information contained in your account. We organize usernames, URLs and encrypted passwords of users to allow them to synchronize this data across all their devices and also to share or bequeath passwords if they choose to do so. SaferPass is not able to access the encrypted passwords because the encryption and the decryption of these passwords occurs on your device with a master password that only you know and SaferPass never stores your master password on any server. If you choose to use our service to share or bequeath passwords to a friend or to tell a friend (e.g. email a friend) about SaferPass, we will request your friend’s email address and automatically send your friend an email inviting him/her to visit the site and create an account. SaferPass stores this information for the sole purpose of sending those emails. Your friend may contact us at any time via support@saferpass.net to request that we remove this information from our database. 5\. USE OF THE INFORMATION. SaferPass uses your personal information to manage your account, to send you information about our Services, to offer you new features or new services, to optimize the Services we already provide to you, to provide updates for the SaferPass Application and to provide better customer service and experience. SaferPass may also use your personal information for statistical purposes. SaferPass may use usage information (as detailed above) to evaluate and improve the features, guest experience and functionality of the Website and/or the SaferPass Application. 6\. SHARING AND DISCLOSURE. SaferPass will share your personal information with third parties only in ways that are described in this privacy statement. SaferPass does not sell, rent or share your personal information with other people, except to: Members of your social networks or members invited by email (e.g. your network/friends/followers on SaferPass, Twitter, email, Facebook or Google+) only if you decide to share certain personal information with them via the Services; Service providers that facilitate our Services, provide any or all part of the Services on our behalf or help us to improve the Services (for example, data storage, web analytics, payment processing and maintenance service providers). These Service providers only have access to the personal information necessary to perform these tasks on our behalf. Our advertising partners so they can provide relevant advertisements or promotional materials on or through the Website and/or the SaferPass Application; and Law Enforcement Officials or Government Agencies (i) in response to an official request; (ii) when permitted or required by law; or (iii) to establish our compliance with applicable laws, rules, regulations or guidelines. These providers and partners are prohibited from sharing or selling this information, and may not use this information for any purpose not described in this section. If SaferPass merges with another company, is subject to a corporate reorganization, sells or transfers all or part of the Website and/or the SaferPass Application, its business assets or shares, or in the event of bankruptcy, it is possible that the limited personal information we possess may be sold, transferred or otherwise shared as part of that transaction. SaferPass may choose to retain a copy of that information post transaction. In choosing to use SaferPass, you acknowledge that our service providers and/or advertising partners, as well as members of your network who may receive your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy or applicable law may be located in countries which have a different level of data protection that in your home country. We may also share with third parties certain aggregated non-personal information about you (such as the type of web browser you use) so as to fully optimize our Services. Third parties are prohibited from sharing or selling this information and may not use this information for any purpose not enumerated in this section. You can opt out of this usage by contacting support@saferpass.net with your request. 7\. COOKIES A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a website's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. SaferPass may set, access or delete certain cookies on your computer for the following reasons: (i) to facilitate your "signing in" on the Website or the SaferPass Application; (ii) to provide you with customized content; (iii) to keep track of preferences you specify while you are using our Services; (iv) to provide general internal and user analytics; (v) to conduct research to improve the content of the Website, the SaferPass Application and the Services; and (vi) to assist in identifying possible fraudulent activities. (vii) to log out users from different websites. If you configure your browser to reject cookies, you may not be able to use certain or all of our Services. 8\. THIRD PARTY COOKIES. The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers is not covered by our Privacy Policy. We do not have access to or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to use our Services. 9\. TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES. We use reputable tools such as Google Analytics, Exponea, HotJar third-party tracking services, which uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate to capture usage and volume statistics. Some of our business partners (e.g., Google Analytics, Exponea, HotJar) do use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by SaferPass only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third-party. 10\. EDITING OR CORRECTING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION. Please notify us if you believe your personal information is inaccurate. You have the right (i) to ask for your personal information to be corrected or updated and (ii) to withdraw your consent to the use of your personal information. To do so, please contact us via support@saferpass.net. Please note that as a result you may not be able to use certain or all of our Services. Please also note that SaferPass cannot edit the important encrypted passwords because the encryption and the decryption of this passwords occurs on your device with a master password that only you know and SaferPass never stores your master password on any server. If you lose your master password, SaferPass will not be able to recover your account. Please don't forget your master password. 11\. SECURITY. We restrict access to personal information to SaferPass employees and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our Services. We make commercially reasonable efforts to protect against loss, misuse, and alteration of your personal information that is under our control. To protect the confidentiality of your personal information, we take appropriate security measures (including physical security measures) and we operate secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we have received it. Please be aware that despite these precautions, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. SaferPass takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying information but we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions regarding the security of the Website or the SaferPass Application, you can contact us at SaferPass, 22 Budkova, Bratislava, 81104, Slovakia or via support@saferpass.net. SaferPass has taken commercially reasonable steps to ensure that its service providers protect the confidentiality and security of your personal information, and to ensure that personal information is processed only for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. 12\. ADDITIONAL POLICY INFORMATION. LINKS TO OTHER SITES. The SaferPass Website or the SaferPass Application includes links to other Websites (e.g. a company blog) whose privacy practices may differ from those of SaferPass. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, that information will be governed by their Privacy Policy. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any website you visit. 13\. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY. YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT ANY DISPUTE OVER PRIVACY IS SUBJECT TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AS WELL AS THE TERMS OF SERVICE FOR THE WEBSITE AND THE SaferPass APPLICATION (INCLUDING THE LIMITATION OF LIABILITY PROVISIONS). 14\. LANGUAGE. The parties hereto acknowledge having expressly required that this Privacy Policy is to be drawn up in the English language. Les parties aux présentes reconnaissent avoir expressément exigé que la présente Politique relative à la protection des renseignements personnels soit rédigée en anglais. 15\. QUESTIONS If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or our privacy practices, we encourage you to contact us at SaferPass, 22 Budkova, Bratislava, 81104, Slovakia or via support@saferpass.net.
